Hugh Johnston fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- Radical Campus files, 1958 - 2004; F-223-1; 2.55 m of textual records 72 sound recordings; Date range: Predominant dates of textual material in the series are 1965-1974. General note: sound recordings are located in series F-223-1-7-2.
  - Background material - Political Science, Sociology, and Anthropology Department, 1966 - 2004; F-223-1-4; 28 cm of textual records
    - PSA strike - photocopied issues of the Peak, 1969, vol. 1, F-223-1-4-0-3 (Archival box - standard 223-14)
    - PSA strike - photocopied issues of the Peak, 1969, vol. 2, F-223-1-4-0-4 (Archival box - standard 223-14)
    - PSA strike - photocopied issues of the Peak, 1969, vol. 3, F-223-1-4-0-5 (Archival box - standard 223-14)
    - CAUT bulletins and an Our Generation article, 1969 - 1972; F-223-1-4-0-6 (Archival box - standard 223-15)
    - PSA affair - photocopied fonds material, vol. 1, 1969; F-223-1-4-0-7 (Archival box - standard 223-15)
    - PSA affair - photocopied fonds material, vol. 2, 1969; F-223-1-4-0-8 (Archival box - standard 223-15)
    - PSA affair - photocopied fonds material, vol. 3, 1969; F-223-1-4-0-9 (Archival box - standard 223-15)
    - PSA affair - photocopied fonds material, vol. 1, 1970; F-223-1-4-0-10 (Archival box - standard 223-15)
    - PSA affair - photocopied fonds material, vol. 2, 1970; F-223-1-4-0-11 (Archival box - standard 223-15)
    - PSA affair - photocopied fonds material, 1970 - 1977; F-223-1-4-0-12 (Archival box - standard 223-15)
    - Journal articles and excerpts of Michiel Horn's book Academic Freedom in Canada: A History, 1995 - 1999; F-223-1-4-0-13 (Archival box - standard 223-15)
    - PSA affair, general material, 1966 - 1971; F-223-1-4-0-14 (Archival box - standard 223-16)
    - PSA affair, general material, 1969 - 2002; F-223-1-4-0-15 (Archival box - standard 223-16)
    - Supreme Court of BC - Wheeldon vs. SFU, 1970 - 1999; F-223-1-4-0-16 (Archival box - standard 223-16)
    - Index to peak issues pertaining to the PSA affair, 2000 - 2004; F-223-1-4-0-17 (Archival box - standard 223-16)
    - Dismissal hearing of Nathan Popkin - SFU Counsel, 1970; F-223-1-4-0-18 (Archival box - standard 223-16)
    - Dismissal hearing of Nathan Popkin, 1970; F-223-1-4-0-19 (Archival box - standard 223-16)
    - Dismissal hearing of Nathan Popkin - Kenneth Strand, 1970; F-223-1-4-0-20 (Archival box - standard 223-16)
    - Dismissal hearing of Nathan Popkin - Dale Sullivan, 1970; F-223-1-4-0-21 (Archival box - standard 223-16)
    - Rosenbluth Committee transcripts - PSA department faculty, 1970; F-223-1-4-0-22 (Archival box - standard 223-16)
  - Miscellaneous background material - Steve Hicks, 1986 - 1989; F-223-1-5; 4 cm of textual records
    Sub-series consists primarily of material related to Steve Hicks' work as Robin Fisher's research assistant. Subjects, events and activities documented student life and the political impetus for the establishment of SFU. Sub-series consists of research notes, interview questions, and drafts of chapters for an unpublished book.
    The arrangement was provided by the archivist.
    Hicks, Steve; Fisher, Robin
    - Steve Hicks - working notes, 1986 - 1989; F-223-1-5-0-1 (Archival box - standard 223-16)
    - Steve Hicks - interview notes, 1986 - 1989; F-223-1-5-0-2 (Archival box - standard 223-16)
    - Steve Hicks - drafts of "Student Life", 1989; F-223-1-5-0-3 (Archival box - standard 223-16)
    - Robin Fisher - Chapter 1 Origins: The premier makes a call, 1989; F-223-1-5-0-4 (Archival box - standard 223-16)
    - RG numbering index, 1986 - 1989; F-223-1-5-0-5 (Archival box - standard 223-16)
  - Miscellaneous background material - C.R. Day, 1963 - 1981; F-223-1-6; 17 cm of textual records
    Sub-series consists of original and photocopied material related to the Senate Committee on Rules and Procedures Pertaining to Professional Conduct. Subjects, events and activities documented include professional conduct at other universities; the Faculty Association Committee on the University Act; legal matters related to professional conduct; university governance; and the Planning Committee on Interior Programming's 1977 report. Sub-series consists of memoranda, correspondence, reports, minutes, newspaper clippings, book excerpts, and drafts of procedures on professional conduct.
    Simon Fraser University Faculty Association; Senate Committee on Rules and Procedures Pertaining to Professional Conduct; Planning Committee on Interior Programming
    Most of this material was given to Hugh Johnston by C. R. Day. Professor Day was the chair of the Senate Committee on Rules and Procedures Pertaining to Professional Conduct from 1971-1972.
    - Senate Committee on rules and procedures pertaining to professional conduct, vol. 1, 1968 - 1969; F-223-1-6-0-1 (Archival box - standard 223-16)
    - Senate Committee on rules and procedures pertaining to professional conduct, vol. 2, 1970; F-223-1-6-0-2 (Archival box - standard 223-16)
    - Senate Committee on rules and procedures pertaining to professional conduct, vol. 3, January 1971 - July 1971; F-223-1-6-0-3 (Archival box - standard 223-17)
    - Senate Committee on rules and procedures pertaining to professional conduct, vol. 4, August 1971 - October 1971; F-223-1-6-0-4 (Archival box - standard 223-17)
    - Senate Committee on rules and procedures pertaining to professional conduct, vol. 5, October 1971 - December 1971; F-223-1-6-0-5 (Archival box - standard 223-17)
    - Senate Committee on rules and procedures pertaining to professional conduct, vol. 6, January 1972 - April 1972; F-223-1-6-0-6 (Archival box - standard 223-17)
    - Senate Committee on rules and procedures pertaining to professional conduct, vol. 7, May 1972 - November 1972; F-223-1-6-0-7 (Archival box - standard 223-17)
    - Senate Committee on rules and procedures pertaining to professional conduct, vol. 8, 1973; F-223-1-6-0-8 (Archival box - standard 223-17)
    - Senate Committee on rules and procedures pertaining to professional conduct, vol. 9, 1974 - 1981; F-223-1-6-0-9 (Archival box - standard 223-17)
    - Draft procedures on professional conduct - February 1972, F-223-1-6-0-10 (Archival box - standard 223-17)
    - Draft procedures on professional conduct - July 5, 1972, F-223-1-6-0-11 (Archival box - standard 223-17)
    - Faculty Association Committee on the University Act, 1971 - 1973; F-223-1-6-0-12 (Archival box - standard 223-17)
    - Senate Committee on rules and procedures pertaining to professional conduct - reports from other universities, 1969 - 1972; F-223-1-6-0-13 (Archival box - standard 223-18)
    - Working Paper on University Governance in BC, 1963 - 1974; F-223-1-6-0-14 (Archival box - standard 223-18)
    - Stanford University - H. Bruce Franklin case, 1971 - 1972; F-223-1-6-0-15 (Archival box - standard 223-18)
    - SFU Planning Committee for Interior Programming 1977 report, F-223-1-6-0-16 (Archival box - standard 223-18)
  - Interviews, 1974 - 2003; F-223-1-7; 19 cm of textual records 72 sound recordings; General note: sound recordings are located in sub-sub-series 2.
    Sub-series consists primarily of interviews with prominent members of the SFU community, including faculty, administrators, and students. Hugh Johnston conducted interviews; however he also collected audiocassette recordings and transcripts of interviews conducted by other researchers. They include Liisa Fagerlund, Ken Nielsen, Elika Kohler, Robin Fisher and Ruth Sandwell. Johnston's research assistants, John-Henry Harter and Dionysios (Dino) Rossi, also conducted interviews. Subjects, events and activities documented include student activism, the governance and administration of SFU, the 1968 CAUT motion of censure, the PSA affair and the history of SFU. Sub-series consists of audiocassette recordings and transcriptions of the interviews.
    Department of Political Science, Sociology and Anthropology; Canadian Association of University Teachers; Sound recordings
    - Interview transcriptions, 1974 - 2002; F-223-1-7-1; 19 cm of textual records; Patricia Johnston transcribed most of the interviews. The archivist printed the electronic versions of the interview transcriptions.
      Sub-sub-series consists of transcriptions of interviews. For a list of interviewees, see file list.
      - Morris Achtemichuk transcription - interviewer John-Henry Harter, 2001; F-223-1-7-1-1 (Archival box - standard 223-18)
        Achtemichuk, Morris; Textual records
      - Heribert Adam transcription - interviewer Dino Rossi, 2002; F-223-1-7-1-2 (Archival box - standard 223-18)
      - Ron Baker transcription - interviewer Robin Fisher, 1988; F-223-1-7-1-3 (Archival box - standard 223-18)
      - Ron Baker transcription - interviewer John-Henry Harter, 2001; F-223-1-7-1-4 (Archival box - standard 223-18)
      - Margaret Benston transcription - interviewer Ken Nielsen, 1982; F-223-1-7-1-5 (Archival box - standard 223-18)
        Benston, Maggie; Textual records
      - Bill Birge transcription - interviewer John-Henry Harter, 2001; F-223-1-7-1-6 (Archival box - standard 223-18)
        Birge, Bill; Textual records
      - Larry Boland transcription - interviewer Dino Rossi, 2002; F-223-1-7-1-7 (Archival box - standard 223-18)
        Boland, Larry; Textual records
      - Tom Bottomore transcription - interviewer Liisa Fagerlund, 1974; F-223-1-7-1-8 (Archival box - standard 223-18)
      - Roy Carlson transcription - interviewer Hugh Johnston, 2002; F-223-1-7-1-9 (Archival box - standard 223-18)
        Carlson, Roy L.; Textual records
      - John Cochran transcription - interviewer Hugh Johnston, 2002; F-223-1-7-1-10 (Archival box - standard 223-18)
        Cochrane, John F.; Textual records
      - Allan Cunningham - interviewer Ken Nielsen, 1982; F-223-1-7-1-11 (Archival box - standard 223-18)
      - Don DeVoretz transcription - interviewer Dino Rossi, 2002; F-223-1-7-1-12 (Archival box - standard 223-18)
        Devoretz, Don; Textual records
      - Stephen Duguid transcription - interviewer Dino Rossi, 2002; F-223-1-7-1-13 (Archival box - standard 223-18)
      - John Ellis transcription - interviewer Hugh Johnston, 2002; F-223-1-7-1-14 (Archival box - standard 223-18)
      - Arthur Erickson transcription - interviewer Ruth Sandwell, 2001; F-223-1-7-1-15 (Archival box - standard 223-18)
      - Harry Evans transcription - interviewer Hugh Johnston, 2002; F-223-1-7-1-16 (Archival box - standard 223-19)
      - Len Evenden transcription - interviewer Dino Rossi, 2002; F-223-1-7-1-17 (Archival box - standard 223-19)
      - John Hutchinson transcription - interviewer Ken Nielsen, 1982; F-223-1-7-1-18 (Archival box - standard 223-19)
        Hutchinson, John; Textual records
      - Ray Jennings transcription - interviewer Dino Rossi, 2002; F-223-1-7-1-19 (Archival box - standard 223-19)
      - Pauline Jewett transcription - interviewer Robin Fisher, 1991; F-223-1-7-1-20 (Archival box - standard 223-19)
      - Bob Koepke transcription - interviewer Ken Nielsen, 1982; F-223-1-7-1-21 (Archival box - standard 223-19)
        Koepke, Robert; Textual records
      - Ruth Lambert transcription - interviewer John-Henry Harter, 2001; F-223-1-7-1-22 (Archival box - standard 223-19)
      - Mike Lebowitz transcription - interviewer Ken Nielsen, 1982; F-223-1-7-1-23 (Archival box - standard 223-19)
      - Archie MacPherson transcription - interviewer Ken Nielsen, 1982; F-223-1-7-1-24 (Archival box - standard 223-19)
        MacPherson, Archibald; Textual records
      - Jane Martin and Norma Marier transcription - interviewer John-Henry Harter, 2001; F-223-1-7-1-25 (Archival box - standard 223-19)
        Martin, Jane; Marier, Norma; Textual records
      - Patrick McTaggart-Cowan transcription - interviewer Robin Fisher, 1986; F-223-1-7-1-26 (Archival box - standard 223-19)
      - Kenji Okuda transcription - interviewer Ken Nielsen, 1982; F-223-1-7-1-27 (Archival box - standard 223-19)
      - Klaus Rieckhoff transcription - interviewer Hugh Johnston, 2002; F-223-1-7-1-28 (Archival box - standard 223-19)
      - Kenneth Strand transcription - interviewer Hugh Johnston, 2000; F-223-1-7-1-29 (Archival box - standard 223-19)
      - Kenneth Strand transcription - interviewer Ken Nielsen, 1982; F-223-1-7-1-30 (Archival box - standard 223-19)
      - George Suart transcription - interviewer Robin Fisher, 1990; F-223-1-7-1-31 (Archival box - standard 223-19)
      - Dale Sullivan transcription - interviewer Elika Kohler, 1983; F-223-1-7-1-32 (Archival box - standard 223-19)
        Sullivan, Dale; Textual records
      - Norman Swartz - interviewer Dino Rossi, 2001; F-223-1-7-1-33 (Archival box - standard 223-19)
      - Chris Taylor transcription - interviewer Dino Rossi, 2002; F-223-1-7-1-34 (Archival box - standard 223-19)
      - John Webster transcription - interviewer Hugh Johnston, 2002; F-223-1-7-1-35 (Archival box - standard 223-19)
        Webster, John M.; Textual records
      - Lolita Wilson transcrption - interviewer Hugh Johnston, 2002; F-223-1-7-1-36 (Archival box - standard 223-19)
      - Sharon Yandle transcription - interviewer Dino Rossi, 2002; F-223-1-7-1-37 (Archival box - standard 223-19)
    - Audiocassette recordings of interviews, 1974 - 2003; F-223-1-7-2; 72 sound recordings
      Sub-sub-series consists of audiocasette recordings of interviews.
      Interviews with consent forms are open but will need to be digitized before access is granted. Interviews without consent forms are pending review and need to be reviewed during digitization.
      An item list is available.
      Physical description: 72 sound recordings are stored on 100 audio cassettes; some recordings have multiple cassettes, some recordings exists in multiple copies.
      - Achetemichuk, Morris - interviewer John-Henry Harter, September 2001; F-223-1-7-2-0-1 (Audio cassette OBJ-3825)
        Morris Achetemichuk; Harter, John-Henry; Sound recordings
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-223-item1.
      - Baker, Ron - interviewer Robin Fisher, July 1988; F-223-1-7-2-0-3 (Audio cassette OBJ-3826, Audio cassette OBJ-3827, Audio cassette OBJ-3828, Audio cassette OBJ-3829)
        Baker, Ron; Fisher, Robin; Sound recordings
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-223-item2, F-223-item3, F-223-item4, F-223-item5.
      - Baker, Ron - interviewer John-Henry Harter, April 2001; F-223-1-7-2-0-2 (Audio cassette OBJ-3830, Audio cassette OBJ-3831)
        Baker, Ron; Harter, John-Henry; Sound recordings
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-223-item6, F-223-item7.
      - Benston, Margaret - interviewer Ken Nielsen, March 1982; F-223-1-7-2-0-4 (Audio cassette OBJ-3832, Audio cassette OBJ-3833)
        Benston, Maggie; Nielsen, Ken; Sound recordings
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-223-item8, F-223-item9.
      - Benston, Margaret - unknown interviewer, July 1982; F-223-1-7-2-0-5; Additional information located while reviewing tape for access: Interview recorded and conducted for Canadian Studies 390/391 class (Audio cassette OBJ-3834)
        Benston, Maggie; van Loon, Marianne; Sound recordings
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-223-item10.
      - Birge, Bill - interviewer John-Henry Harter, August 2001; F-223-1-7-2-0-6 (Audio cassette OBJ-3835)
        Birge, Bill; Harter, John-Henry; Sound recordings
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-223-item11.
      - Boland, Larry - interviewer Dino Rossi, May 2002; F-223-1-7-2-0-7 (Audio cassette OBJ-3836)
        Boland, Larry; Rossi, Dionysios; Sound recordings
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-223-item12.
      - Bottomore, Tom - interviewer Liisa Fagerlund, August 1974; F-223-1-7-2-0-8 (Audio cassette OBJ-3837)
        Bottomore, Tom B.; Fagerlund, Liisa; Sound recordings
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-223-item13.
      - Camley, Amanda - interviewer John-Henry Harter, July 2001; F-223-1-7-2-0-9 (Audio cassette OBJ-3838, Audio cassette OBJ-3839)
        Harter, John-Henry; Camley, Amanda; Sound recordings
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-223-item14.
      - Carlson, Roy - interviewer Hugh Johnston, November 2002; F-223-1-7-2-0-10 (Audio cassette OBJ-3840)
        Carlson, Roy L.; Johnston, Hugh; Sound recordings
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-223-item16.
      - Cochran, John - interviewer Hugh Johnston, December 2002; F-223-1-7-2-0-11 (Audio cassette OBJ-3841)
        Cochran, John; Johnston, Hugh; Sound recordings
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-223-item17.
      - Cunningham, Allan - interviewer Ken Nielsen, March 1982; F-223-1-7-2-0-12 (Audio cassette OBJ-3842)
        Cunningham, Allan B.; Nielsen, Ken; Sound recordings
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-223-item18.
      - DeVoretz, Don - interviewer Dino Rossi, August 2002; F-223-1-7-2-0-13 (Audio cassette OBJ-3843, Audio cassette OBJ-3844)
        Devoretz, Don; Rossi, Dionysios; Sound recordings
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-223-item19.
      - Duguid, Steven - interviewer Dino Rossi, January 2002; F-223-1-7-2-0-14 (Audio cassette OBJ-3845)
        Duguid, Steve; Rossi, Dionysios; Sound recordings
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-223-item21.
      - Ellis, John - interviewer Hugh Johnston, Part I, October 2002; F-223-1-7-2-0-15 (Audio cassette OBJ-3846)
        Ellis, John F.; Johnston, Hugh; Sound recordings
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-223-item22.
      - Ellis, John - interviewer Hugh Johnston, Part II, November 2002; F-223-1-7-2-0-16 (Audio cassette OBJ-3847)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-223-item23.
      - Erickson, Arthur - interviewer Ruth Sandwell, 8 July 2001; F-223-1-7-2-0-17 (Audio cassette OBJ-3848, Audio cassette OBJ-3849, Audio cassette OBJ-3850, Audio cassette OBJ-3851)
        Erickson, Arthur; Sandwell, Ruth; Sound recordings
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-223-item24.
      - Evans, Harry - interviewer Hugh Johnston, October 2002; F-223-1-7-2-0-18 (Audio cassette OBJ-3852, Audio cassette OBJ-3853, Audio cassette OBJ-3854)
        Evans, Harry M.; Johnston, Hugh; Sound recordings
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-223-item28.
      - Evenden, Len - interviewer Dino Rossi, August 2002; F-223-1-7-2-0-19 (Audio cassette OBJ-3855, Audio cassette OBJ-3856)
        Evenden, Len; Rossi, Dionysios; Sound recordings
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-223-item31.
      - Hutchinson, John - interviewer Ken Nielsen, March 1982; F-223-1-7-2-0-20 (Audio cassette OBJ-3857, Audio cassette OBJ-3858)
        Hutchinson, John; Nielsen, Ken; Sound recordings
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-223-item33.
      - Jennings, Ray - interviewer John-Henry Harter, January 2002; F-223-1-7-2-0-21 (Audio cassette OBJ-3859)
        Jennings, Ray E.; Harter, John-Henry; Sound recordings
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-223-item35.
      - Jewett, Pauline - interviewer Robin Fisher, June 1991; F-223-1-7-2-0-22 (Audio cassette OBJ-3860)
        Jewett, Pauline; Fisher, Robin; Sound recordings
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-223-item36.
      - Koepke, Bob - interviewer Ken Nielsen, March 1982; F-223-1-7-2-0-23 (Audio cassette OBJ-3861)
        Koepke, Robert; Nielsen, Ken; Sound recordings
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-223-item37.
      - Lambert, Ruth - interviewer John-Henry Harter, July 2001; F-223-1-7-2-0-24 (Audio cassette OBJ-3862)
        Lambert, Ruth; Harter, John-Henry; Sound recordings
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-223-item38.
      - Lebowitz, Mike - interviewer Ken Nielsen, March 1982; F-223-1-7-2-0-25 (Audio cassette OBJ-3863, Audio cassette OBJ-3864)
        Lebowitz, Michael; Nielsen, Ken; Sound recordings
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-223-item39.
      - MacPherson, Archie - interviwer Ken Nielsen, March 1982; F-223-1-7-2-0-26 (Audio cassette OBJ-3865)
        MacPherson, Archibald; Nielsen, Ken; Sound recordings
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-223-item41.
      - Martin, Jane and Norma Marier - interviewer John-Henry Harter, April 2001; F-223-1-7-2-0-27 (Audio cassette OBJ-3866)
        Martin, Jane; Marier, Norma; Harter, John-Henry; Sound recordings
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-223-item42.
      - McTaggart-Cowan, Patrick - interviewer Robin Fisher, September 1986; F-223-1-7-2-0-28 (Audio cassette OBJ-3867, Audio cassette OBJ-3868, Audio cassette OBJ-3869)
        McTaggart-Cowan, Patrick; Fisher, Robin; Sound recordings
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-223-item43.
      - Okuda, Kenji - interviewer Ken Nielsen, March 1982; F-223-1-7-2-0-29 (Audio cassette OBJ-3870)
        Okuda, Kenji; Nielsen, Ken; Sound recordings
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-223-item46.
      - Rieckhoff, Klaus - interviewer Hugh Johnston, October 2002; F-223-1-7-2-0-30 (Audio cassette OBJ-3871, Audio cassette OBJ-3872, Audio cassette OBJ-3873, Audio cassette OBJ-3874)
        Rieckhoff, Klaus E.; Johnston, Hugh; Sound recordings
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-223-item47.
      - Strand, Kenneth - interviewer Hugh Johnston, Part I, November 2000; F-223-1-7-2-0-31 (Audio cassette OBJ-3875, Audio cassette OBJ-3876, Audio cassette OBJ-3877, Audio cassette OBJ-3878)
        Strand, Kenneth; Johnston, Hugh; Sound recordings
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-223-item51.
      - Strand, Kenneth - interviewer Hugh Johnston, Part II, February 2001; F-223-1-7-2-0-32 (Audio cassette OBJ-3879, Audio cassette OBJ-3880)
        Johnston, Hugh; Strand, Kenneth; Sound recordings
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-223-item55.
      - Strand, Kenneth - interviewer Hugh Johnston, Part III, 2001; F-223-1-7-2-0-33 (Audio cassette OBJ-3881, Audio cassette OBJ-3882, Audio cassette OBJ-3883)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-223-item58.
      - Strand, Kenneth - interviewer Ken Nielsen, 11 March 1982; F-223-1-7-2-0-34 (Audio cassette OBJ-3893)
        Strand, Kenneth; Nielsen, Ken; Sound recordings
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-223-item69.
      - Suart, George - interviewer Robin Fisher, April 1990; F-223-1-7-2-0-35 (Audio cassette OBJ-3884)
        Suart, George; Fisher, Robin; Sound recordings
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-223-item60.
      - Sullivan, Dale - interviewer Elika Kohler, March 1983; F-223-1-7-2-0-36 (Audio cassette OBJ-3885, Audio cassette OBJ-3886)
        Sullivan, Dale; Kohler, Elika; Sound recordings
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-223-item61.
      - Swartz, Norman - interviewer Dino Rossi, December 2001; F-223-1-7-2-0-37 (Audio cassette OBJ-3887, Audio cassette OBJ-3888)
        Swartz, Norman; Rossi, Dionysios; Sound recordings
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-223-item63.
      - Taylor, Chris - interviewer Dino Rossi, January 2002; F-223-1-7-2-0-38 (Audio cassette OBJ-3889)
        Rossi, Dionysios; Taylor, Chris; Sound recordings
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-223-item65.
      - Webster, John - interviewer Hugh Johnston, December 2002; F-223-1-7-2-0-39 (Audio cassette OBJ-3890)
        Webster, John M.; Johnston, Hugh; Sound recordings
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-223-item66.